Promise Tshegofatso Magoga

■ tshegofatsopromise362@gmail.com

**** 0664464167

Pretoria, South Africa

R Portfolio website

in LinkedIn

GitHub

Profile

I am a young energetic, optimistic and a hardworking web and mobile app developer with 1-2 years of experience in building user-friendly applications using react native, react js and flutter.I am also proficient in developing and integrating backend using Nodejs and firebase. I am an open minded person who loves to solve problems through tech. My objective is to work in an environment which encourages me to succeed and grow professionally where I can utilize my skills and knowledge appropriately

Education

2022 - 2022 Mobile Application Development: React Native (NQF Level 5)

Remote, South Africa I.T Varsit

This course was offered by I.T Varsity in partnership with MTN Business and

MICTSETA:

Programming languages: Html, Css, javaScript

Frameworks: React.js, React Native

Database: Firebase

2018 - 2021 Matric (NQF Level 4)

Pretoria, South Africa Kgadime Matsepe Secondary School

Subjects: Physical Science, Mathematics, Geography, Life Sciences, Life Orientation,

English FAL, Sepedi

Professional Experience

2023/06 – present Pretoria, South Africa

Software Developer Trainee

mLab (CodeTribe Academy)

- I developed a hotel management application using react.js, bootstrap, material ui and firebase. This application had two sides, which is the admin and client site. The admin had the privilege to add new rooms, update rooms and hotel information and the client only had the privilege to view and book the rooms.
- I developed a restaurant mobile application using react native and firebase. The application allowed the user to view the menu, add items to cart, remove items from cart, increase and decrease quantity. Also integrated stripe payment gateway to take care of the payment for the orders.
- Currently we are working on a group project for a client, which for now the project will remain anonymous, and am assigned as a front end developer. We will be using react native, firebase and redux for state management.

2023/03 – 2023/03 Remote, South Africa

Web Developer (freelancer)

Limitless Horizon (PTY) LTD

• I developed a landing page for an egg business, using html, css, javaScript and bootStrap.

Technical Skills

Web and Mobile App development

HTML5, CSS3, javaScript, React, React Native,

Bootstrap, Material UI, Node.js

UI Design

Figma, Webflow

Databases

Firebase, MongoDB, SQLite, Local Storage

 \bullet

. . . .

Git, GitHub, NPM, Vscode

Soft Skills

Problem Solving

Collaboration

Creativity

Certificates

Mobile Application Development ☑

React Native

Webflow design ☑ Intro to Webflow Series

Scrum Alliance 🛮 Scrum Foundation

Backend development 2 Node.js and mongoDB

References

Vukona Mnisi, CodeTribe Facilitator, mLab vukona@mlab.co.za, 0128440240

Lindani Ricardo Mabaso, Project Manager, Limitless Horizon (PTY) LTD 0711171524